Tom Miller papers, 1852-2003 (Bulk 1950-2003)
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Series I: Publications by Tom Miller
  - Subseries 1: Articles
    - Animal defenders Horn in on Sheep Hunters. Crawdaddy Feature, March 1979 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - AmerMex After Villa. The New York Times. New York, April 7, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - A profitable love-hate relationship in the border zone. The Arizona Daily Star, April 10, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Bisbee should Declare War. Serving Sierra Vista and Bisbee, May 7, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - The Great American Chili Craze. Saga, August 1979 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - On the Border: Life Begins on The Other Side. Geo, November 1979 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - New Yorker, December 17, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Hispanic Groups Seek A New Federal Trial In Arizona Alien Case. The New York Times. New York, NY, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Breakfast of Champions. Rocky Mountain Magazine, January-February 1980 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Result of Border Bullet: Wheelchair and Regrets. The New York Times, January 14, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Border Industrial Programs. Mule Mountain Observer, February 20-March 5, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Baja's Blues. New West, February 25, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Frontiere-piege pour les peones. Geo, March 1980 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Ronstadt Hopes to Record Big Profit. New West, March 10, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - How To Be A Cunning Linguist. Tucson Weekly News. Tucson, Arizona, April 2-8, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Habitual Offenders Act Is Under Scrutiny in Texas. The New York Times. New York, NY, April 13, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - Black Sect in Shootout Says It Won't Return to Arizona Home. New York Times, June 2, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - Which page of the Arizona Daily Star d'ya read? The New Yorker, June 23, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - Trial Opens Today for Ranchers In Assault on Mexican Laborers. The New York Times, June 26, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - Arizona Ranchers' Jury Protested. The New York Times, June 27, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - U.S. Prosecutors Protest Jury Selection in Arizona. The New York Times, June 27, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - Mexican Tells Jurors of Border Ordeal. The New York Times, July 2, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - Mexican Role Visible in U.S. Trial of Arizona Ranchers. The New York Times, July 7, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - Jurors Hear Closing Arguments In the Alleged Torture of 3 Aliens. The New York Times, July 25, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - Aerial Burial. Playboy, August 1980 (Box 3, Folder 45)
    - 2 Smuggler of Refugees Enter Guilty Plea in Arizona. The New York Times, September 25, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 46)
    - Aliens Smuggler Is Found Guilty By Arizona Jury: 13 Salvadorans Perished in Trip through Desert. New York Times, October 7, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 47)
    - Arizonan is charged with putting an illegal Mexican alien in chains. New York Times, October 9, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 48)
    - Prayers Seek Action in Tucson Slaying. The New York Times, October 9, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 49)
    - Prayers Seek Action in Tucson Slaying. The New York Times, October 9, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 50)
    - 2 Men Get 5-Year Terms In Alien-Smuggling Case. The New York Times, October 21, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 51)
    - Florida Grower Accused in Alien Smuggling Ring. Tom Miller Contributed. New York Times, November 12, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 52)
    - Hanigan Verdict: Why they got off. New Times Weekly, November 23-30, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 53)
    - Waterbed smothers girl. The Realist, November 30, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 54)
    - Second Body Is Found in Gulf of California Search. The New York Times, December 1, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 55)
    - Arizona ranchers face third trial in 1976 beating of 3 Mexicans. The New York Times, January 20, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 56)
    - 2 juries to weight Mexican charges: panels selected to try Arizonans accused of torture - judge rebuffs race-bias pleas. The New York Times, January 24, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 57)
    - Jury hears new witness in retrial of 2 ranchers charged in beatings. The New York Times, February 12, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 58)
    - 3 New witness testifies in retrial of ranchers charged in beatings. The New York Times, February 12, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 59)
    - Arizonan Convicted In Beating Of Aliens: Second Jury Frees His Brother on Federal Charges in Attack on 3 Mexican Farm Workers. The New York Times, February 24, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 60)
    - A Fashion Fable. Playboy, March 1981 (Box 3, Folder 61)
    - A Mexican Laborer Tells of Chaining: Defense in Arizona Case Concedes Rancher Locked Up Employee. The New York Times, April 1, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 62)
    - Arizona Rancher Is found Guilty Of Chaining Mexican Farmworker. New York Times, April 10, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 63)
    - Sonoyta Interlude From "On the Border". Tucson's Mountain Newsreal. Tucson, Arizona, April 10-May 8, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 64)
    - Acquitted rancher is held on drug charge in Arizona. The New York Times, April 16, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 65)
    - Rancher gets a three-year jail term for beating and robbing Mexicans. The New York Times, April 21, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 66)
    - Historic School, Modern Problems. The New York Times, April 25, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 67)
    - U.S. Border Agents Accused of Racism. The New York Times, May 3, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 68)
    - Complaints of Bias on Border Patrol Under Inquiry. The New York Times, May 3, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 69)
    - Searching for Al Capone's imported bar. The Arizona Republic Sunday Magazine, May 17, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 70)
    - Pancho Villa Statue Unveiled in Arizona. The New York Times, July 2, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 71)
    - A Missionary's Legacy on the Arizona-Sonora Border. The New York Times, August 9, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 72)
    - A Drive on the Wild Side: Excerpts from "On the Border". New Times. Phoenix, AZ, August 12-18, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 73)
    - Museum Displays Bogus Art Given by Unwitting Sponsor. The New York Times, August 16, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 74)
    - The Mystery of a Missing Naturalist May Lead to Legal Test of Dismissal. The New York Times, August 16, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 75)
    - Bracero Program No. 3. The New York Times, October 5, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 76)
    - Bracero proposal No. 3 lacks compassion for the laborer. The Arizona Daily Star. Tucson, AZ, October 6, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 77)
    - The Border Blasters. Music and Sound Output, November / December 1981 (Box 3, Folder 78)
    - A Big Weekend for Antelope Wells, N.M., Pop. 2. The New York Times, December 15, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 79)
    - Mexican Strike Ends, Freeing Produce for U.S. New York Times, January 10, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 80)
    - Udall Is Making a Choice Between Two Districts. New York Times, January 17, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 81)
    - What's Doing in Tucson. The New York Times, February 14, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 82)
    - Debt to Paraplegic Could Shut Town. The New York Times, April 13, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 83)
    - The Great Candy Exchange. Bisbee Times, May 1982 (Box 3, Folder 84)
    - Reunion Recalls Movie on Hispanic Strikers Made at Time of Film Blacklist. The New York Times, May 3, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 85)
    - South Tucson Again Told To Pay Man $4 Million. The New York Times, May 6, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 86)
    - Strangers across the border: the kids of Mexico and Arizona look across the line at their lives. Empire Magazine (Denver Post), June 20, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 87)
    - Cuernavaca Language Schools: Learning to speak Spanish, Mexican-style. Diversion, October 1982 (Box 3, Folder 88)
    - Decline of Copper Mining Stimulates a Community's Search for New Industry. The New York Times, October 19, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 89)
    - What's Doing in Scottsdale. The New York Times, October 24, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 90)
    - Rancher in Plea to High Court in Case of Tortured Mexicans. The New York Times, December 5, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 91)
    - Ex-Hostage's Family Praises Play on Ordeal. The New York Times, December 6, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 92)
    - New Leader Is Sworn In By Navajo Indian Nation. The New York Times, January 12, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 93)
    - 135000 Navajos' New Leader: Peterson Zah. The New York Times, January 14, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 94)
    - Folk Arts Thrive In a Quito Shop. The New York Times, January 16, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 95)
    - Navajo New Order. The New York Times, January 16, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 96)
    - Viva Villa! from On the Border. Coyote, March 1983 (Box 3, Folder 97)
    - The Tastiest Little Book Tour In Texas. Diversion, March 1983 (Box 3, Folder 98)
    - What's Doing In San Salvador. The Village Voice. New York, NY, May 24, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 99)
    - James Watt and Friends, Live Onstage: Another Opening, Another Show. New Times, May 25-June 1, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 100)
    - You visited Ecuador? The Christian Science Monitor, June 6, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 101)
    - Operation Not Fade Away: Who Killed Buddy Holly? Buddy, September 1983 (Box 3, Folder 102)
    - Obscurity shelters peaceful Ecuador. New York Times?, September 11, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 103)
    - For Scientists, a Revisit To '45 Atomic Blast Site. The New York Times, October 3, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 104)
    - Laughlin, Nev.: A draw. Chicago Tribune. Chicago, IL, November 13, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 105)
    - U.S. towns in exchange with Soviet. The New York Times, November 25, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 106)
    - Class Reunion: Salt of the Earth Revisited. Cineaste, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 107)
    - City at the 'Middle of the World': Quito is just south of the Equator and nearly two miles high. The New York Times, January 22, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 108)
    - An Old West Cemetery for Jews Is Rededicated at Tombstone. The New York Times, February 29, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 109)
    - A bloom on the desert. Northwest Orient, March 1984 (Box 3, Folder 110)
    - Casino community relies on boat trade. The Denver Post. Denver, CO, March 4, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 111)
    - Court curbs a use of news reports. The New York Times, August 11, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 112)
    - On the Border: a visit to nearby border towns. Bisbee Magazine, Fall 1985 (Box 3, Folder 113)
    - Especial: La Frontera. Miami Mensual, December 1985 (Box 3, Folder 114)
    - Sandinistas should get the U.S. Aid, not Contras. The Arizona Daily Star. Tucson, AZ, March 20, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 115)
    - Ecuador Is Brimful of Panama Hats. New York Times, August 3, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 116)
    - A Great Restaurant of the Western World. Playboy, September 1986 (Box 3, Folder 117)
    - Awakening to the Snorin' Desert. New Times. Phoenix, AZ, September 10-16, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 118)
    - Scratching an Offbeat Itch: If it looks like a chicken and sounds like a chicken... it must be Papago. New Times, September 17-23, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 119)
    - Going the Way of All Groceries. New Times. Phoenix, AZ, September 24-30, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 120)
    - Governing the Indians. New Times, October 1-7, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 121)
    - Tales Told in Our Barrio: Hispanic history in the making. New Times, October 8-14, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 122)
    - Ode to a Chimichanga: The gastronomical equivalent of war is not a crudely built cable suspension bridge. New Times. Phoenix, AZ, October 15-21, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 123)
    - Viva la Chimichanga! The Tucson Weekly. Tucson, AZ, October 22-29, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 124)
    - The Embattled Beanfield: Robert Redford's film-in-progress captures the Chicano rebels of Milagro. New Times. Phoenix, AZ, November 19-25, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 125)
    - Indians of the Andes Protest Their Chains. Newsday, December 19, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 126)
    - Milagro: Breaking New Ground: Can Robert Redford Bring John Nichols' Embattled Beanfield to the Screen? The Tucson Weekly. Tucson, AZ, December 17-23, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 127)
    - Brief Encounter: An ex radical confronts an ex Attorney General. New Times. Phoenix, AZ, January 28-February 3, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Cause for El Arma! The demise of Alarma!, Mexico's sleaziest tabloid, gave guts-and-gore publishing a place in the Sun Belt. New Times. Phoenix, AZ, March 4-10, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Striking Out in Court. New Times. Phoenix, AZ, April 29, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - New Law May Shape the U.S.-Mexico Borderland. Newsday. New York, May 6, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Special to The Washington Post. Of Trails and Trailblazing. The Washington Post. Washington, D.C, May 31, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Trail Mix: New friends and old on a traveler's road. Chicago Sun-Times. Chicago, IL, June 7, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Banana Republic Catalog, Summer 1987 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Band of allies can't be broken. The Arizona Daily Star. Tucson, AZ, June 21, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Trail Mix: Celebrating the Joys of Trekking. The Tucson Weekly. Tucson, AZ, July 22-28, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - It may be... Movieline, July 24, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Hits Y Misses (in Playboy After Hours). Playboy, August 1987 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - A Little Hell on Earth: Or is the Sierra del Pinacate some strange paradise? Even this Mexican wasteland has its protectors. New Times. Phoenix, AZ, December 16-22, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - A Little Hell on Earth: Or is the Sierra del Pinacate some strange paradise? Even this Mexican wasteland has its protectors. New Times. Phoenix, AZ (Copy 2), December 16-22, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - The Base Buoys the Market. New York Times. New York, December 20, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Sierra Club Trail Calendar, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - A Fragile Paradise: In Search of the Soul of El Pinacate. The Tucson Weekly. Tucson, AZ, January 13-19, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - What's Doing in Tucson. New York Times. New York, February 21, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Latin American Fiesta. The Washington Post. Washington, DC, April 3, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Venality + Buffoonery = Mecham's Fatal Flaw. Newsday, April 18, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Letters From Guadalajara: Publishers Persevere. Albuquerque Journal. Albuquerque, NM, May 10, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - The Latin American Omnibus. Independent Traveler, June 11, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - A Daring Display of Defeat Trough the Ages! And all under one roof. Welcome to the Museum of Intervention. New Times. Phoenix, AZ, August 3-9, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Sorry, in Europe, the Natives Are Not Impressed. Newsday, August 21, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - The Pristine Wasteland Of the Pinacates. The Washington Post. Washington, D.C, August 28, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Behind the Scenes in Havana. Islands September/October, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - 'Smokeless' Cigarette's Rough Debut. New York Times. New York, November 20, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Thirdcoast Vol.24, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Thirdcoast Vol.25, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Thirdcoast Vol.28, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Thirdcoast Vol.29, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Thirdcoast Vol.30, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Thirdcoast Vol.31, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Thirdcoast Vol.32, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Thirdcoast Vol.32 (Copy 2), 1988 (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - Thirdcoast Vol.33, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - This Brew's for You. Arizona Trend, January 1989 (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - The Working Man's Romeo and Juliet: In search of Rosie and the 'Open Pit Mine'. Arizona Trend, February 1989 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Eau de Saguaro: The French connection to Arizona can be a little, well, gauling. Arizona Trend, March 1989 (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - Straw Boss: The incomparable - but misnamed - Panama hat. Travel & Leisure, March 1989 (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - Hopi Scrabble: A scholarly labor of love documents a living Indian language. Arizona Trend, April 1989 (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - Edge City: If you think New York or D.C. is what a city should be, one expert has a suggestion for you: consider Phoenix, instead. Arizona Trend, May 1989 (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - Creamed Chicken: In Ehrenberg, if you're good you're good, and if you're bad they bring the wheelbarrow. Arizona Trend, June 1989 (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - Crying Fowl: 'Our only failing is that we like to watch roosters fight.'. Arizona Trend, July 1989 (Box 4, Folder 43)
    - Briefcase Buckaroos: From forgettable food to fake cactus, kitsch-conscious New Yorkers embrace things 'Southwest.'. Arizona Trend, August 1989 (Box 4, Folder 44)
    - Velvet Art: This medium sends a message. Is it trash? Is it art? Can it solve the illegal immigrant problem? Arizona Trend, September 1989 (Box 4, Folder 45)
    - Operation Not Fade Away: Who Killed Buddy Holly? Buddy, September/October 1989 (Box 4, Folder 46)
    - Dear Diary: A week as a Nielsen family can tell you a lot about yourself - or not. Arizona Trend, October 1989 (Box 4, Folder 47)
    - Casa Grande Dreamin': Meet me at half past 8 ... at the ball game. Arizona Trend, November 1989 (Box 4, Folder 48)
    - Bantam Battles: Slice 'N' Dice Derbies Still Draw spectators. A Day Of Cockfighting At The Copper State Game Club. The Tucson Weekly. Tucson, AZ, November 8-14, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 49)
    - Chinavajo: A little taste of Peking in Tuba City. Arizona Trend, December 1989 (Box 4, Folder 50)
    - Will Castro stay the course? Chicago Tribune. Chicago, IL, December 20, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 51)
    - Cubans hear echoes of E. Europe revolt. The Plain Dealer. Cleveland, OH, December 25, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 53)
    - Descubriendo el Corazon de La Bamba. Mas; In Spanish, Summer 1990 (Box 4, Folder 54)
    - Gun Shy: In Phoenix, they're perfecting pistols and pondering 'people control.'. Arizona Trend, January 1990 (Box 4, Folder 55)
    - Cuba Stays the Course -- Still. The Sun, January 7, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 56)
    - Of dogma and Rodney Dangerfield. The Times of the Americas, January 10, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 57)
    - Castro May Be Immune to Communism's Collapse: Unlike his counterparts in Eastern Europe, Cuba's leader still seems to retain the affection of his people. Newsday, January 11, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 58)
    - Cuba holds firm on communism. Philadelphia Inquirer, January 23, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 59)
    - Traveler's Miscellany. Outside, February 1990 (Box 4, Folder 60)
    - Do Not Pass Go: With this new game, you too can make the harrowing Run for the Border. Arizona Trend, February 1990 (Box 4, Folder 61)
    - The Bold Murals Of Tucson's Streets: An egalitarian art blends three southwestern cultures. The New York Times. New York, NY, March 4, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 62)
    - Light at the End of the Tunnel is Green. Arizona Daily Star. Tucson, Arizona, May 31, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 63)
    - The Velvet Parade: Along the border, Visions of a Wondrous Art Form. The Washington Post. Washington, DC, September 30, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 64)
    - Investing the Southwest. Journal of the Southwest, Winter 1990 (Box 4, Folder 65)
    - Links with the Past: At the Wigwam, Arizona's five-star desert hotel. Travel & Leisure, December 1990 (Box 4, Folder 66)
    - 912. Sex, Spies and Literature. Graham Greene's Cuba: Helping Fidel was the Heart of the Matter. Washington Post, April 14, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 67)
    - Sex, Spies and Literature. Miami Herald, April 21, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 68)
    - Recorido por la Habana de Graham Greene. El Nuevo Herald, April 22, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 69)
    - Get off your tie horse: Real wranglers wear bolas. Travel & Leisure, May 1991 (Box 4, Folder 70)
    - In Search of Graham Greene's Cuba. Cuba Update, Summer 1991 (Box 4, Folder 71)
    - Mexico's Copper Canyon: Adventure and spectacular scenery aboard the Chihuahua-Pacifico railroad. Diversion, June 1991 (Box 4, Folder 72)
    - The Mild West: Arizona. Travel & Leisure, October 1991 (Box 4, Folder 73)
    - The Mild West: Arizona. Travel & Leisure (Copy 2), October 1991 (Box 4, Folder 74)
    - The Mild West: Arizona. The Bisbee Observer, October 31, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 75)
    - Missing Chapter: The Persian Gulf War Awaits its Great Novel. (With Gregory McNamee) Tucson Weekly, November 27, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 76)
    - The Gulf War Awaits Its Great Novel. (With Gregory McNamee) Bloomsbury Review, December 1991 (Box 4, Folder 77)
    - Bringing up the Cuban rear. New Times (Miami). Miami, FL, November 18-24, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 78)
    - The event that inspired the movie and the play. The New York Times. New York, December 6, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 79)
    - Searching for the Heart of La Bamba. Hemispheres. Greeensboro, N.C, December 1992 (Box 4, Folder 80)
    - Fade-Out in Havana. Los Angeles Times Magazine. Los Angeles, December 20, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 81)
    - In Castro's closet. Playboy (in Playboy After Hours). Chicago, December 1992 (Box 4, Folder 82)
    - Bambalogy. Hemispheres, March 1993 (Box 4, Folder 83)
    - Little Havana's triple play. Hemispheres. Greensboro, N.C., April 1993 (Box 4, Folder 84)
    - Writers we love... The Outback Times ("a publication for the at-large members of the National Writers Union"). Tucson, AZ, April 1993 (Box 4, Folder 85)
    - A trade embargo that has long outlived its purpose. Los Angeles Times (Opinion); Los Angeles, April 11, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 86)
    - The Cuban bestseller list: hotcakes in Havana. Los Angeles Times (Book Review). Los Angeles, April 25, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 87)
    - Castro, a reluctant landlord, won't cash the rent check. New York Times. New York, June 16, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 88)
    - Thinking of an 'enemy' as a partner. Arizona Daily Star. Tucson, June 22, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 89)
    - La Bamba. Sing Out! Bethelehem, PA, May/June/July 1993 (Box 4, Folder 90)
    - For peace, bread, and roses -- Cuba remembers the Rosenbergs. Cuba Update. New York, Summer 1993 (Box 4, Folder 91)
    - Hemingway, Cuba inextricably linked. San Antonio Express-News. San Antonio, August 1, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 92)
    - In a tailspin, but still intoxicating. Travel & Leisure. New York, October 1993 (Box 4, Folder 93)
    - Is there a sweet by and by? New York Times. New York, NY, March 6, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Why go to Cuba? Hemispheres. Greensboro, N.C., April 1994 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Waiting for the end in Cuba. Life. New York, May 1994 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Vanishing America. Nostalgia ain't what it used to be. Lands' End Direct Merchants. Dodgeville, Wisc., June 1994 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Vanishing America. Books ahoy! Lands' End Direct Merchants. Dodgeville, Wisc., July 1994 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Vanishing America. The write stuff. Lands' End Direct Merchants. Dodgeville, Wisc., August 1994 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Cuba: Bedeviled Island. Washington Post, August 17, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Playing macho with Cuba is futile. Newsday. Melville, New York; Viewpoints, August 25, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - End of the affair. With Cuba in crisis, the Left's romance with Castro is over. Washington Post [Outlook]. Washington, D.C., September 4, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Twilight in Havana. Tucson Weekly, November 24-30, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Shelf Involved. American Way, January 15, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Ten myths about Cuba: Isolation, embargo spawn half-truths about Castro's land. San Antonio Express-News, March 26, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - I Remember Jerry. Tucson Weekly, April 27-May 3, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Real Castro, Cuba obscured by myth. Arizona Republic, April 30, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Real Castro, Cuba obscured by myth. Arizona Republic (Copy 2), April 30, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Bad Blood in New Mexico. Washington Post Book World, May 14, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Jesse Helms: Our Man in Havana? (Letter From Cuba) Newsday, June 11, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Ten misconceptions about today's Cuba. San Jose Mercury News, July 2, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 18)